

MOCH RIFQI RAMDHANI

081393003129 | rifqiramdhani8@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rifqi-ramdhani-5b49b1208/ | https://github.com/rifqiramdhani

Perum bukit berlian C72, padalarang

I am a backend developer with 3 years of experience in building and managing server infrastructure, databases, and APIs for web applications. In the last 3 months, I have also attended a full-stack developer bootcamp where I have deepened my knowledge and skills in web application development from both the frontend and backend perspectives. Additionally, I learned about teamwork, collaboration, and project management. The combination of my experience as a backend developer and a full-stack developer has enabled me to develop more effective and efficient web applications in the future.

Work Experiences

Asia-pasific Urban Designers - Jakarta, Indonesia

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Web Developer

- · Redesign old website
- · Re-create the company profile along with the CMS page for members and admin.
- · Create a registration form every time there is a recent event.

Code X Academy - Jl. Bukit Golf Hijau No.131RW.8, Cijayanti, Kec. Babakan Madang, Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat 16810 Dec 2022 - Mar 2023

Team Lead

- · Leads and cooperates with 7 members
- · Build a website for booking a hotel
- · Create website pages to manage human resources

Education Level

CodeXAcademy - Jl. Bukit Golf Hijau No.131RW.8, Cijayanti, Kec. Babakan Dec 2022 - Mar 2023 Madang, Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat 16810

Bootcamp in Fullstack Nodejs

Indonesia Computer University - Jl. Dago No. 160-162, Kota Bandung, Jawa Barat Sep 2018 - Dec 2022 40132

Undergraduate in Informatics Engineering, 3.35/4.00

SMAN 1 Cimahi - Jl. Pacinan No.22 A, Cimahi, Kec. Cimahi Tengah, Kota Cimahi, Jan 2014 - Jan 2017

Jawa Barat 40525

High School in IPA

Organisational Experience

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika (HMIF) UNIKOM - Bandung, Indonesia

Oct 2019 - Oct 2021

Member of Pengembangan Wawasan Teknologi Informasi

- · Conduct research on efforts to improve and develop the quality of UNIKOM Informatics Engineering Student resources.
- Formulate a movement strategy pattern to take a role in the dynamics of the world of lectures in the UNIKOM Informatics Engineering academic field.
- · Managing the UNIKOM Informatics Engineering Study Program Library

Skills

- Hard Skills: Html, Css, Javascript, Php, Python, Typescript, Node Js, Codeigniter, Laravel, Django, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Nest Js, Next Js
- · Soft Skills: Leadership, Problem Solving, Public Speaking, Teamwork, Critical Thinking